// const dayEightQuestions = [
//   {
//     question:
//       "What is the state of purity in which all pilgrims enter Makkah for Hajj called?",
//     options: ["Adhaan", "Ihram", "Istikhara", "Ababa"],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Which Islamic principle does the Hajj demonstrate?",
//     options: [
//       "Importance of children",
//       "Equality and universal brotherhood",
//       "Importance of charity",
//       "Celebrations",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "What is the name of the place where the pilgrims pelt stones on pillars representing the devil?",
//     options: ["Al-Jamarat", "Mina", "Muzdalifa", "None of the above"],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "What is considered to be the most important part of the Hajj?",
//     options: [
//       "When pilgrims circumambulate the Kaabah",
//       "When pilgrims stone the Pillars representing the devil",
//       "The day the pilgrims spend praying on the Plains of Arafah",
//       "Days spent in Mina and Muzdalifah",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "How many times do the Muslims circumambulate the Kaabah?",
//     options: ["One Time", "Three Times", "Five Times", "Seven Times"],
//     correctOption: 3,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "During which month is the Hajj performed?",
//     options: ["Dhul-Hijjah", "Ramadhan", "Muharram", "Rajjab"],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "What is Hajj?",
//     options: [
//       "Pilgrimage to Shrines",
//       "Pilgrimage to Monasteries",
//       "Pilgrimage to Makkah (Saudi Arabia)",
//       "Family Get-together",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "What do Muslims recite during and throughout the Hajj?",
//     options: [
//       "Al-Fatiha",
//       "Taalbiya",
//       "Declaration of Hajj",
//       "There is no specific recitation",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "How many times do Muslims have to perform Hajj in their lifetime?",
//     options: [
//       "Every year",
//       "Once in five years",
//       "Once in a decade",
//       "Once in their lifetime, if they are physically and financially able",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 3,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "What does the running or swift walking of pilgrims seven times between the hills of Safaa and Marwah represent?",
//     options: [
//       "The number of times the Prophet Muhammad performed the Hajj in his lifetime",
//       "The number of times the Prophet Abraham (PBUH) tried to build the Kaabah before he succeeded",
//       "The number of times Hagar ran back and forth between the hills searching for water for her son, Prophet Ishmael (PBUH)",
//       "The number of miles the Prophet Muhammad travelled from Medina to Mecca to perform the Hajj",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
// ];
// export default dayEightQuestions;
const dayEightQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which surah (chapter) of the Quran was revealed first?",
    options: ["Surah Al-Fatiha", "Surah Al-Baqarah", "Surah Al-Alaq", "Surah Al-Ikhlas"],
    correctOption: 2,
    justification: "The first revealed surah was Surah Al-Alaq. (Quran 96:1-5)"
  },
  {
    question: "Where did the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) pass away?",
    options: ["Mecca", "Medina", "Jerusalem", "Taif"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "The Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) passed away in Medina."
  },
  {
    question: "How many children did the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) have?",
    options: ["2", "4", "6", "7"],
    correctOption: 3,
    justification: "The Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) had 7 children."
  },
  {
    question: "What year did the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) pass away?",
    options: ["20 AH", "9 AH", "11 AH", "13 AH"],
    correctOption: 2,
    justification: "The Prophet (PBUH) passed away in 11 AH."
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the Prophet Muhammad's (PBUH) father?",
    options: ["Abdullah ibn Abdul Muttalib", "Abdul Muttalib", "Abu Talib", "Abu Bakr"],
    correctOption: 0,
    justification: "The Prophet's father was Abdullah ibn Abdul Muttalib."
  },
  {
    question: "Which wife of the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) was known as the 'Mother of the Believers'?",
    options: ["Khadijah bint Khuwaylid", "Aisha bint Abi Bakr", "Hafsa bint Umar", "Zainab bint Jahsh"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "Aisha (RA) was known as 'Mother of the Believers'."
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the Prophet Muhammad's (PBUH) paternal uncle who supported him during his early years of prophethood?",
    options: ["Abu Sufyan", "Abu Lahab", "Abu Talib", "Hamza ibn Abdul Muttalib"],
    correctOption: 2,
    justification: "Abu Talib was the Prophetâ€™s uncle who supported him."
  },
  {
    question: "In which battle did the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) lose his uncle Hamza?",
    options: ["Battle of Uhud", "Battle of Badr", "Battle of Khandaq", "Battle of Hunayn"],
    correctOption: 0,
    justification: "Hamza (RA) was martyred in the Battle of Uhud."
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the tribe that expelled the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) from Mecca?",
    options: ["Quraish", "Banu Umayya", "Banu Hashim", "Banu Nadir"],
    correctOption: 0,
    justification: "The Quraish tribe forced the Prophet (PBUH) to leave Mecca."
  },
  {
    question: "How old was the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) when he received the first revelation?",
    options: ["30 years", "40 years", "50 years", "35 years"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "The Prophet (PBUH) was 40 years old when he received the first revelation."
  }
];


export default dayEightQuestions;